https://www.pirelli.com/tyres/en-gb/cookie-policy

PAGANIPORSCHETIPSALL ARTICLESSAFE DRIVING AND TYRE FEATURESEU TYRE LABELWINTER DRIVINGFIND YOUR DEALERKeep In TouchMyPirelliCar/Cookie PolicyCOOKIE POLICYThis website (“Website”) collects and processes personal data. Such personal data is used to identify your computer, browser or any other mobile device that you use to surf the Internet. Personal data is collected through the Website by means of small software files and other tracking technologies (“Cookies”).
The Website uses technical, analytics and profiling Cookies that are installed directly by us (first party Cookies) or by selected third parties (third party Cookies).
The technical Cookies used on the Website are classified as Necessary Cookies. These Cookies are necessary to enhance your browsing experience and guarantee the core functionality of the Website.
Analytics Cookies are third party Cookies used for statistical purposes and collect information in an aggregated and anonymous form (for example, they are used to count user visits on the Website).
The profiling Cookies used on the Website are classified as Marketing Cookies. These Cookies are installed through the Website by third parties in order to display targeted advertising customized according to the preferences you expressed during the browsing session (for example, when you visit some pages of the Website or interact with the Website’s features). Your consent is necessary for the installation of such Marketing Cookies.
The table below explains the cookies we use, their category and the applicable cookie policy.
Source
Cookie Name
Cookie Domain
Cookie Type
Cookie Policy
Pirelli
AWSELB
.pirelli.com
Statistic
https://support.mouseflow.com/support/solutions/articles/44001550895-what-is-your-cookie-policy-
Oracle Eloqua
ELOQUA
.pirelli.com
Marketing
https://www.oracle.com/legal/privacy/marketing-cloud-data-cloud-privacy-policy.html
Facebook
_fbp
.pirelli.com
Marketing
https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy
Facebook
fr
.facebook.com
Marketing
https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy
Maxymiser
mmapi.store.p.0, mmapi.store.s.0mmapi.store.p.0, mmapi.store.s.0
.pirelli.com
Marketing
https://docs.oracle.com/cloud/latest/marketingcs_gs/OMCGB/cd-api/cookies/
Oracle BlueKai
bku, bkdc
.bluekai.com
Marketing
https://www.oracle.com/legal/privacy/marketing-cloud-data-cloud-privacy-policy.html
Google
1P_JAR
.google.com
Marketing
https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en-GB
Google
NID
.google.com
https://policies.google.com/technologies/types?hl=en-GB
The Website includes also content sharing functions on social media. When using these functions, social media platforms may collect information about you, such as your IP address, the pages you visited or the Cookies containing your personal data. Please note that the privacy policies of those social media platforms, some of which are linked below, regulate such processing.
Facebook
Google and YouTube
Twitter
How do I change my cookie settings?
When you access the Website for the first time, a short notice on the use of Cookies will appear as a pop-up. Such pop-up will also include a link to this Cookie Policy.
By clicking the ‘Accept’ button on the pop-up you will provide your consent to the installation of all the Cookies.
Alternatively, you can set your cookie preferences by clicking on the ‘Manage your preferences’ button and then adjust the available sliders to ‘On’ or ‘Off’. Preferences can be changed at any time directly from this page. Click here
If you prefer, you can also set your browser to refuse the installation of Cookies by default or delete all installed Cookies from your computer or mobile device.
The procedure varies according to the browser used. You can access the relevant settings of some of the most popular browsers on the market via the following links:
Google Chrome
Microsoft Edge
Mozilla Firefox
Microsoft Internet Explorer
Opera
Apple Safari
Please note that disabling technical Cookies may affect how the Website functions.
You can opt-out from third party Cookies by referring to third parties’ websites and relevant cookie policies listed above.
PAGANIPORSCHETIPSALL ARTICLESSAFE DRIVING AND TYRE FEATURESEU TYRE LABELWINTER DRIVINGPIRELLI DEALERSFIND YOUR DEALERABOUT USWHY PIRELLIPIRELLI PERFORMANCE CENTREBURTON PIRELLI PERFORMANCE CENTREModern Slavery StatementsCompany InformationContact UsCopyright © 2020 Pirelli & C. S.p.A. - Pirelli Tyre S.p.ALEGAL INFORMATIONUK LEGAL INFORMATIONPRIVACY NOTICESCOOKIE POLICYWORK WITH USDon’t miss out on any Pirelli news! Insert your email to receive exclusive updates Email* Car Brand*SelectCar Model*SelectBy ticking this box I hereby authorise the processing of my Personal Data by email for the purpose of direct marketing in accordance with the Privacy Notices *Mandatory fields Subscribe
